<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English Posts on Ashley's Blog</title><link>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/posts/</link><description>Recent content in English Posts on Ashley's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Personalized Decision Making - A Conceptual Introduction (Scott Mueller and Judea Pearl)</title><link>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/2023/01/12/causal-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/2023/01/12/causal-1/</guid><description>Abstract This paper
clarifies the distinction between personalized decision making, which targets the behavurir of a specific individual, population-based decision making, which concerns a sub-population resembling that individual, explains why personalized decision making leads to more informed dicisions. The authors argued that combining experimental and observational studies can
obtain valuable information about individual behavior, improve decisions over those obtained from experimental studies alone. 1.</description></item><item><title>Markdown Testing</title><link>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/2022/11/24/second-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/2022/11/24/second-post/</guid><description>See the source code of this page if you are interested.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 List Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Table Water Water Water Water Water Water Water Water1 Water Water Water Water Quotes What I cannot create, I do not understand2.</description></item><item><title>The Road Not Taken</title><link>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/1915/01/01/road-not-taken/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 1915 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://Ashleygua.github.io/en/1915/01/01/road-not-taken/</guid><description>Two roads diverged in a yellow wood,
And sorry I could not travel both
And be one traveler, long I stood
And looked down one as far as I could
To where it bent in the undergrowth;
Then took the other, as just as fair,
And having perhaps the better claim,
Because it was grassy and wanted wear;
Though as for that the passing there
Had worn them really about the same,</description></item></channel></rss>